# Laura Hulley

Squamish, Canada

☑ hulleylm@gmail.com

(+1) 778-955-3338

**?** /hulleylm

hulleylm.github.io

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Whistler Core

Climbing Guide

April 2024 - Now | Whistler, Canada

- Created **digital marketing** content for email and social channels using **Adobe Illustrator**. Increased Instagram engagement by up to **100%**.

# Parthian Climbing.....

Community Engagement Manager Jun 2023 - Mar 2024 | London, UK

- Developed **digital marketing strategies** and events to engage the local community.

# Substation Brixton

Centre Manager

Jan 2022 - May 2023 | London, UK

- Regularly **updated and maintained** the company Wordpress site.
- Improved site **SEO**.
- **Troubleshooting** any website and technical issues, and working quickly to resolve.

# AVA Security.....

Engineer - 1 month contract

Aug 2021 | London, UK

- Writing **Python scripts** to catagorise large databases of images for use as training data for Machine Learning models.

## University of Liverpool.....

Technology Team Intern

Aug 2021 | Liverpool, UK

- Building **custom tools to optimise work efficiency** for the team. Including a browser extension, linked forms with automated emails, and a host of web-scraping scripts.
- **Creating bespoke websites** within short timeframes for virtual events during covid. Utilised by >1,000 students and employers.
- **Communicating technical information** to colleagues in different departments. Writing **clear documentation** to ensure new tools were **accessible** to the team.

# **PROJECTS**

#### LandGAN

#### view on GitHub

A Generative Adversarial Network trained with satellite and elevation data to produce "unlimited" new terrains.

- One of the **first recorded uses** of GANs for terrain generation.

# Google Maps Tiler.....

#### view on GitHub

A Python script that allows the results of the Google Elevation API to be seamlessly tiled into a larger image.

- Created in response to a Stackoverflow question. **Marked as useful** by a number of users.

#### **SUMMARY**

Junior software developer with experience building and maintaining websites and digital marketing projects. Passionate about combining technology and design to make accesible and engaging sites. A hard worker and quick learner, excited by the opportunity to progress my skills further.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **University of Liverpool**

BSc (with Hons) - Computer Science First Class degree

- President of the Windsurfing Society
- Won the "Persuasion award" at the Village Software Data Quest.

#### Read the write up

#### **SKILLS**

#### **Experience** with

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Python
- LATEX
- Wordpress
- GIT
- Adobe Suite

#### Knowledge of

- PHP
- Perl
- Node.js

#### **COMMUNITY**

#### **Ignite Your Future Hackathon**

 Led a team of three students to organise a virtual hackathon, with a panel of industry professional judges.

#### **SWA**

 Volunteered as a committee member for the National Student
Windsurfing Association, organising low-cost and accessible events for students with up to 400 attendees.